So friends welcome to one of our videos
friends today I have brought such an application for you by
using it you
can earn 40 to 50 thousand rupees every month and
yes in the app you will get 500 rupees for every transaction
friends you will get 500
rupees for every transaction so let me tell you which one
is that sorry pro friends friends till now there is a
lot of trouble in this disease you will
definitely get it for every transaction and
you will also be able to get instant relief
in your bank so friends let's move
towards the video
before this whole matter moves forward if you are
new to our channel then definitely subscribe to the channel
and yes if you do
not want to miss our mute then you should
also press the bell icon and put it on all so
that you get the notification of all our videos as
soon as possible and yes
friends if you are also a subscriber to our telegram channel then
definitely join us here to get
hurt
in its grip our Ghagra has to be done with tempered
glass now quickly chant 108 mantras
and like here you will see search reality
Our channel keeps posting a lot of benefits,
whatever apps profit, I do
n't have to make a video of it, so you have done this a lot of
times, so we know that turn it
on quickly, let's start, first of all I will
show you on payment,
as soon as you write doctor here,
many options will come to you,
like if you click on reaction, you will be given
₹500 here, you will get 520 on this invite,
friends, this is not a small thing,
Ratan Tata himself has invested in it
and this is a very big app, hence
you are getting signals of 500, 1000 and it is
written here that you will
also get 1 gram gold coin, so
friends, this is a very good application, it is
giving it absolutely free of cost, it is a
Junoon app and I myself use it,
I myself like it very much, so
as soon as you open it, I
will search for it as per difficulty, click
here, major rank listeners also saw that
Hindustan got ₹500  ₹500 ₹400 ₹500 here
and I will show you
how much money you have received after receiving ₹500 ₹500, it is
absolutely alive friends, there is no lie here, nothing
else, it is absolutely correct
and there is a text option here, you will
directly send it, this dandruff will be
transferred to the bank and I
cannot show you the entire money here, I have done it right,
YouTube is against magnet left,
it destroys you completely, so
as you see, you will put your clipping here
and immediately you will see that there will be a
quick
rebate, so there is no need to worry
friends, you can send
500 500 rupees, see, I have ₹1000 sitting with me to
withdraw and the rest and I have
money, I can show it, so the mosque will show
you like you, you will add it on the link,
you will directly start it till now and
as soon as this first option will
come, you have to click on deficit in this phone,
in greater and after that you will see here  You have to
put your tomato on it and give your mobile number,
click from the center, so like after that
you have to put your PAN card symbol and date
of birth here, now there is no need to worry,
you can enter the end result in the same
format and here you have UC, next you are a
Kshatriya, then you will get this CID
in the description and I
trust you on the skin skin and
yes you will show the update in bike collision
and friends, from the PAN card, some tension
friends and your ID from here will also be
visible on the description and it will be
shown on the screen, then you have to enter it,
but let me
tell you that after setting up your today, click here
and the list will come, here you have to choose the date of
birth but it is Monday, so
as you use it, you have to
enter it here and it will ask you whether you are a matchmaker or a
female, whatever you will ask and single
Mukesh or canvas will ask for them,
enter anything from the front, it is only formative present
inside and you will be asked here today
political exports, you have to enter this PIN
and if you want to know behind  You have to turn back and do sector,
friends benefit, hey, here it will
ask you whether you pay tax
on your country India, so you have to click on it
and after that there is a word here, you have to
click on decoration, so
friends, after that you have to click on next, then
you will see two options here,
priority and basic, then you have to click on
basic, yes, the second option
which is given, of course you have to click on it and
after that you will see a coupon code
option, in which offers are canceled,
Facebook is opened, like a tablet
can come when Meghnad's hunter, after this
congratulations will appear, you will have to enter
your account number here, if you want
your money to go in that, then it is
important to look at it, friends, you should check the account number of that only,
you will make the correction, you will give
your account number which is entered in the PAN card,
here the account safe is there, so I will
click on saving from my account
and you have to click on the point where it will ask you to
nut without any document,
so you have to
select here  Whatever you want to do, you have to sign
your signature on the account of the person
whose account you have, I will
give an example of a senior mother like Kareena, like my
account is Ajay Kumar, I will
upload it like this, I will show you the proof of income here,
you have to click on the ID, you have to click there and on the right there is an
income proof option, even if you
give it, it will be fine, there is no need to be afraid,
I am going to give it myself, you have to click on next, the question
mark will be shown here, after this it will be shown to you
that you have to sign your account, you
can do this here, you will get it
and it has to be linked with
mobile Aadhar OTP, if
you do not have the subscribe button,
click on it,
mobile number should be linked with Aadhar,
you will click on it, if
not then click on the friend's name, if we have it, then we will do it
for animals, then
this option comes to us, get the Aadhar ID,
after that we will click on OK here,
you will have to enter the Aadhar number here,
as there are spices  We will enter
our Aadhaar number and we will get an OTP on that. The OTP will be
verified.
Here it will tell us to enter it. We will have to enter
our virtual Aadhaar ID.
After entering it here, we will click on generate. After entering the turn off key, we will put our
rose on the side of the application. So, we
will click here. As soon as we
click on sign up, we will get a
security code on our mobile, so we will
enter it. We will click on it and we will do it
from here as well. We will do it
scientifically and here we will be asked to
enter our Aadhaar number FIRST. So, we will enter our Aadhaar number here
so that the OTP will come on that only.
Please enter the OTP on the mobile number plate which is active. So,
you will enter it here. After that, we will
click on St. Martin and
recharge the TV by entering it and click on submit
button. After that,
press here and it will ask us to check your
wallet. We will deposit
₹10 in your bank for confirmation.
This deposit will be done immediately by your bank.  After that
you will get more information here
that half of you will get another
process now in this you will have to
upload the video in which you have to
take the video of your Aadhar card and upload it like if it is a human Aadhar
card then you should
show your face in front of your face here, once in front
and once behind, maximum make a video from 15th to 20th August
and by doing it in front and behind you
will simply upload it to show your chest
completely, just
show yourself on chat, it will be done when friends it will be
written here that the application has been submitted
successfully, no false message will come, I will
show you the app of regret,
like you open it here, it
is scientific and I will tell you how to do different
things, so friends as soon as
you type it here, it will automatically appear, if you
click on this point here, such an
interface will appear in front of you in which you
can share your link with anyone through WhatsApp or SMS, so as
you share your link
on WhatsApp,
as I show you by doing it, you will share
this link with your friends  You have to
send it to your relatives, if anyone
copies the link from this then the investment
leaders will get five, friends you will get
unlimited, so this is that if
you have many bank accounts, PAN card,
Aadhar card, then you can copy the
link in it and send it to your mobile,
put your own record of getting a lot of money in it, subscribe to all, you will get it easily in this,
if you have many bank accounts you will
get more money, so friends, if you
can easily earn a lot of money by doing this, so friends, if you liked the video then
like it, comment and
definitely share the video and wait
for our New Delhi, till then bye-bye
thank you friend